快看  太不可思议了
Check it out, this is unbelievable!
乔伊已经憋气将近四分钟啦
Joey's been holding his breath for almost four minutes.
伙计  你想闷死我啊
Dude, You trying to kill me?
-菲比  问你件事  -什么事
- Pheebs, l want to ask you something. -Uh, what?
看在我要搬出去  而你又这么美丽...
Since l'm moving out, and you're so beautiful...
我搬去跟你住如何
...how about l move in with you?
当然好啦  可是狄妮丝怎么办呢
That would be great, but what do we do about Denise?
-谁是狄妮丝  -我的室友啊
- Who's Denise? - My roommate.
你有室友啊
You have a roommate?!
是啊  人家叫狄妮丝  狄妮丝
Yes, Denise. Denise!
菲比  你干嘛这么神秘
What is with the secrecy, Phoebe?
这个狄妮丝如何  可爱吗
What about Denise? She cute?
菲比  我不懂  我们怎么会不知道
Pheebs, I don't understand. How can you have a roommate
你有室友这件事呢
that none of us know about?
或许是因为从来没人认真听我说话
Maybe because you never listen to anything that l say.
我一天到晚提起她  狄妮丝
l talk about her all the time. Denise!
瑞秋  我在想
Hey, Rach, listen, I was think,
我那里会多一个房间
l'm gonna have an extra room over at my place.
-那倒是  -对啊  你何不搬来跟我住
- That's true. - Yes. Why don't you move in with me.
我们可以谈心到天明  看看电影
It’ll be great! We can like, stay up late talking, and watch movies.
你知道赤裸星期四的规定吧
You know about naked Thursdays, right?
是啊  我想  我还是自己找房子好了
Yeah, yeah. l think l'll find my own place.
我以为赤裸星期四是我们的专利呢
l thought naked Thursdays was just our thing, man.
你没去注销你们的婚姻
What did Rachel say when you told her
瑞秋怎么说
you were still married to her?
那个啊
Oh, that.
她挺能接受的啊
She took it really well.
-你没说对吧  -没有
- You didn't tell her, did you? - No.
就知道你不会说  因为你还爱着她
Of course not, because you're in love with her.
我并不爱她
l am not in love with her.
她正为了搬家的事情伤心呢
She was very upset about having to move out.
所以我没告诉她这件事
So I didn't tell her we were still married,
免得她更不开心
'cause she would only get more upset.
我只是以朋友的身分安慰她
I...l comforted her. As a friend.
你是怎么个"安慰"法
What do you mean "comforted her"?
也没什么  我就抱了抱她
Nothing. l just gave her a hug.
拥抱正是爱情的经典表现
Ah-uh, a classic sign of love, the hug.
这也是友情的表现啊
lt's also a sign of friendship.
没错  但你不是那个意思  痴情男
Yeah, not in your case, "Lovey Loverson."
那只是个拥抱
lt was a hug.
好吧  那你告诉我
All right, just tell me this,
你有没有闻她的头发
Did you, or did you not, smell her hair?
闻她的头发
Smell her hair?
如果有呢
What if l did?
女性的费洛蒙有九成  是从头部散发
Ninety percent of a woman's pheromones come out top of her head.
所以女人都比较矮
That's why women are shorter.
好让男人在拥抱时爱上她们
So that men will fall in love when they hug them.
拜托  罗斯  你可是科学家啊
Come on, Ross, you're a scientist.
我是以朋友的身分去抱她
l was hugging her as a friend.
又不是我要把脸埋进她的头发里
lt's not my fault, her hair got in my face.
是她头发太多  而且有一股...
She's got a lot of it, and it smells all...all...
椰子香
...coconutty.
怎样
What?
那并不代表我对瑞秋有感觉
lt doesn't mean l have feelings for Rachel.
或许让我有感觉的是椰子
Maybe it means l have feelings for coconuts.
随你怎么说  但你要小心  知道吗
Okay, whatever you say. But just be careful, all right?
瑞秋的想法和你不同
Rachel's not in the same place you are.
好吧  如果这个心情是指爱情
Okay, if the place you're referring to is being in love...
那她的想法和我的一样
...she is in the same place as me,
因为我完全没想法
because l am not in that place.
好吧  我没听懂
Okay, l didn't understand that.
不过或许是
But you know maybe that's
因为你讲的是爱的秘语
because you were speaking the secret language of love.
-伙计  刚才有你的电话  -谁呀
-Dude, some guy just called for you. - Who was it?
不知道
l don't know.
你怎么不谢我帮你留言  什么人啊
How about "Thanks for taking the message"? Jeez!
听着  等你搬进来后
Hey, listen. You know when you move in...
瑞秋的房间就空出来了
...Rachel's room will be empty.
-你想谈谈要怎么利用吗  -当然
- You wanna talk about what to do with it. - Sure.
好  我在想我们应该弄个漂亮的客房
Okay, l was thinking we should have a beautiful guest room, right?
有红木雪橇床
...with a mahogany sleigh bed
床头桌上永远插着鲜花
and bedside tables with fresh flowers all the time.
我们可以弄张折叠式的椅子  上面放留言卡
And we can have a roll-top desk with that little comment cards
好让客人留言  说他们有多喜欢住在这里
so people could tell us how much they love staying here.
不管怎样  我还没有想太多
Whatever, l really haven't thought about it that much.
我喜欢这个主意  当然喜欢
Well, l like that idea...obviously.
我在想或许...
l was thinking maybe...
可以弄个游戏房
maybe it could be a game room, you know.
我们可以买旧的游戏机
I mean you can buy old arcade games,
像太空入侵者和小行星  只要两百元
like Space lnvaders and Asteroids...for $200.
要买真的  要买大的  超大的
The real ones. The big, big, big ones!
不要
No.
你说"不"的意思是  "天啊  钱德勒
Okay so you mean no as in, "Gee, Chandler,
这个主意很有趣
what an interesting idea.
我们先讨论再全盘否定"
Let's discuss it before we reject it competely."
对不起
l'm sorry.
很有趣的主意  可以讨论  但是不行
lnteresting idea. We could talk about it. But no.
没有商量的余地吗
So that's it?
我觉得漂亮的客房不适合放游戏机
l just don't think that arcade games go in a beautiful guest room...
漂亮的客房应该是满屋子古董
the beautiful guest room is gonna be filled with antiques.
所以最适合放小行星了
Which is why Asteroids is perfect.
那可是最古老的游戏机
lt's the oldest game.
你对漂亮的客房有什么意见吗
What do you have against a beautiful guest room?
没有  我对漂亮的客房没有任何意见
Nothing, l don't have anything against a beautiful guest room.
尤其是我们认识的人
Especially since everybody that we know
都住在方圆数公尺内
lives about 30 seconds away.
你是在讽刺我吗
Are you mocking me?
不  我才没嘲笑你或你漂亮的客房
No, l'm not mocking you or your beautiful guest room.
怎么了
What's up?
没事  莫妮卡和我为了无聊的事情吵架了
Nothing, Monica and l had a stupid fight.
但你们还是要同居  对吧
But you're still moving in together, right?
我的广告今天都出来了
'Cause my ad came out today.
"诚征女性室友  不抽烟  不难看"
"Wanted: Female roommate, nonsmoker, nonugly."
漂亮
Nice.
我是觉得在你之后
l just figured, you know, after living with you...
换个女室友应该会蛮有趣的
it'd be interesting change 99 to have a female roommate, you know.
一个可以让我学习的人
Someone l could learn from.
一个和我不一样的人
Someone who is different than me.
而谁和我最不一样
And what's more different than me,
是年过19的男人
a guy who's not 19...
还是19岁的女孩呢
...than a girl who is 19?
我可不是草包  朋友
Not just a hatrack, my friend.
菲比  我想问...
Pheebs, l have to ask you- -
我正忙着呢
l'm swamped right now.
你只是在放空
You're just staring into space.
我正试着用念力移动那支铅笔
l'm trying to move that pencil.
-这支吗  -成功了
- This one? - lt worked!
菲比  找房子真是恶梦
Pheebs, this whole apartment thing is a nightmare.
只要是我租得起的地方
Every place l can afford comes with a roommate
都有怪胎室友  你看这个
who is a freak. I mean, look at this.
"诚征女性室友
"Wanted: Female roommate,
不抽烟  不难看"
nonsmoker, nonugly."
根本没有房子  纽约都住满了
It's just there is  nothing. This city is full.
等等  不  你看这里
Wait! No, look at this!
"两房两卫
"Two bedroom, two bath.
不得抽烟  撒旦教徒可"
Must be nonsmoker. Satan worshipers okay."
可惜  可惜房子是在一楼
No. Yeah, but it's on the ground floor.
瑞秋  你还在找房子吗
Rach, you still looking for a place?
-对啊  怎么了  -听着
- Yeah, why? - Okay.
我们博物馆的华伦
This guy, Warren, from the museum
要去参与挖掘工作两年
is going on a dig for two years.
他有个漂亮的家要转租
And he's got this great place he needs to sublet.
你有兴趣吗
So you interested?
听起来不错
That sounds great!
我愿意住华伦家  我爱华伦
l'd love to live at Warren's. l love Warren!
-谢谢你  -别谢我
- Thank you! - Don't thank me.
要谢就谢那座火山
If you wanna thank someone thank the volcano
几千年前爆发  在毁灭的同时
that erupted thousands of years ago...killing,
也完美保存了一整个文明
but perfectly preserving, an entire civilization.
这是华伦的电话
Here's Warren's number.
太好了  我现在就打给他  谢谢你
This is great. l'm gonna call him right now! Thank you!
好  去打电话吧
Okay, you go call him.
我看到了
l saw it.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what are you talking about?
我在说你知道却又不肯承认的事
l'm talking about what you already know but won't admit.
你又爱上她了  你重新爱上她
You know, you love her again. You re-love her.
我没有重新爱上她
l do not re-love her.
真不敢相信你居然这么嘴硬
l can't believe you won't just admit it.
好吧  总之你千万别做蠢事
Okay, just promise me you won't do anything stupid.
我们现在只是朋友  知道吗
We're just friends now, okay?
我为什么会做蠢事
Why would l do anything stupid?
房子已经租出去了
Well, the apartment is already subletted.
我绝望了  我永远也找不到房子
I mean this is just hopeless. l'll never gonna find anything.
你可以来跟我住啊
You can live with me.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?!
我说什么了
What?
天啊  你是说真的吗
Oh, my god. Are you serious?
我求之不得呢  罗斯
l would love to live with you, Ross
太好了  谢谢你
That's great. Thank you.
有帮到你就好
l'm just glad, you know, l could help you out.
哇  我真替你们高兴
Wow, l'm so happy for you guys.
此举真是一点也不蠢
This is so, so, not stupid.
罗斯  你无法想象这对我有多重要
Ross, Ross, you have no idea what this means to me.
我差点就要流落街头
l mean, I was gonna be homeless.
你救了我  你是我的英雄
You just saved me. You're my hero.
说英雄就太...也行吧
Hero? l don't know. Well, all right.
我要去告诉莫妮卡  她的哥哥有多棒
l have to go tell Monica what a wonderful brother she has.
别这样
Oh, please.
你又有话要说了  对吧
You're gonna say things now, aren't you?
不  我没有
No. No, l won't.
但是我要告诉你
But l should tell you this.
这跟我室友狄妮丝的遭遇如出一辙
This is the exact same thing happened to my roommate, Denise.
她搬去跟一个偷娶她的人住
She moved in with a guy who was secretly married to her.
他嘴上说不爱她  其实心里爱得要死
He said he didn't love her, but he really did.
后来事情败露
And it just blew up.
所以她才搬来跟我住
And that's how she ended up living with me.
好吧  我骗你的
Okay, that's a lie.
刚才很抱歉
Listen, l'm sorry about before.
我不需要游戏房
l don't need to have a game room.
我是因为以前找不到女友
I mean, when I was a kid, l only played those games
才去打游戏的
because l couldn't get girls.
而现在我能找...
Now l can get- -
现在我有了你
Now l have you.
不  我并不是把你当成
No, not that l think l have you...
或想成任何形式上的一件财产
...or think of you as property in any sort of way.
-我对女人...  -别说了  钱德勒
- l see women....- Stop it, Chandler.
我也很抱歉
l'm sorry too.
-真的  -对  当然
- Really? - Yeah. Oh, yes.
钱德勒  我们不必把它弄成客房
Listen, we don't have to made it a guest room
我们可以一起想要怎么利用
We can think of something to do with the room together.
好主意
That's a great idea.
要做到皆大欢喜很容易
We can easily think of a way for us both to enjoy the room.
就是啊
Totally.
-我们不必现在就想  -好
- We don't have to think of it now. - Good.
要不这样
Hey, you know what?
我们来想想客厅要怎么变化
Why don't we think about changes we can make in the living room.
变化
Changes?
对啊  我们得移动一些家具
Yeah, we'll have to move some furniture
好腾出地方放我的椅子
to make room for my chair.
你要把安乐椅搬过来吗
You're bringing the Barcalounger over here?
有问题吗
ls that a problem?
那是一套家具
lt's just that they're a set
或许摆在一起比较好
and they should probably stay together.
那好  那我就全搬过来
That's cool. l'll bring them both over.
你听听
See now, now?
你是要它们离开老家
You're taking them away from their home.
好吧  我懂了  我一无所有
Okay, l get it. So l get nothing.
这里没我的东西  只有你的东西
Nothing here is mine. Everything is yours.
我早上起床  然后穿上你的衣服去上班
l'll get up in the morning, put on your clothes and head off to work!
对  没错  真是够了
Yeah, yeah, you know what? That's it, that's it.
这里只有我的东西  没有你的
Everything will be mine. Nothing will be yours.
我就说了怎么着
That's what I am saying.
拜托  钱德勒  我是在讲安乐椅
Oh, come on, Chandler. l'm talking about the Barcalounger.
它跟这里不搭配  你要把它放到哪里
lt just, it doesn't match. Where will it go?
游戏房里
ln the game room!
你的椅子丑爆了  又不是我的错
lt is not my fault your chairs are incredibly ugly.
好  好  我知道了
All right, that's fine, that's fine.
我不会把椅子搬过来
l won't bring over the chairs.
我什么都不搬过来
l won't bring anything over!
我可不想破坏老奶奶家的格调
l wouldn't want to ruin the ambiance over here at grandma's place!
你的条件看起来很好
Everything on your application looks really good.
最后一个问题
Just one last question.
你和你朋友会不会常来这里
Are you and your friends gonna be over here all time,
比如狂欢聚会之类的
like partying and hanging out?
放心  我不太爱玩
Don't worry. l'm not really a party girl.
别想都不想就说
Don't just be blurting stuff out.
我要你想清楚再答
l want you to really think about your answers.
你不必找室友了
You call off the roommate search.
你好  我要住在这里
Hi. l'll be living here.
别听他乱说
Don't listen to him.
他只是个很想住进来租客
He's just some guy who wants the apartment.
但我不会选他
But I don't think he's going to get it.
你干嘛把浴帘摘掉
Why did you took the shower curtain down?
因为那个东西有安全隐忧
That thing was a hazard!
我非常注重安全
l'm very safety conscious.
我正在为你的东西腾出点空间
l was just clearing some space for your stuff.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
听着  我在莫妮卡家
But listen, I was just as Monica's,
她和钱德勒大吵了一架
she and Chandler had a big fight
所以现在不打算同居了
and they're not moving in.
什么叫不同居了
What do you mean, not moving in?
他们还是要同居  对吧
They're still moving in, right?
不  他们就怎么利用我的房间
No, no, they just had a big blowout
而大吵一架
over what to do with my room.
搞什么  就为了一个烂房间吗
What? Over a stupid room?
是啊  我为他们难过  但也开心
l know, I feel kind of bad for them, but I also really excited,
因为我不必搬过来了
cause now l don't have to move in here!
没错  这一点的确很棒
Oh, no. Yeah, that part's great.
你们两个到底是在吵什么
What's all this about you guys fighting?
真的就为了一个房间吗
ls this really over a room?
那也太傻了吧
I mean, that is so silly.
-罗斯  我们自己可以摆平  -显然不行
- Ross, We can handle this. - Apparently not.
我不能眼睁睁看着
And l can't just stand by and watch
两个我如此关心的人
two people l care about so much...
为了这么傻的事而伤感情
...be hurt by something that is so silly.
别再犯傻了
I mean, enough of the silliness.
那你干嘛不叫她别犯傻了
Why don't you tell her to stop being silly.
双方都有理
Two very good points.
我认识你们两个很久了
Look, l've known you both a long time.
而且在你们在一起前  我从未见过你们
And l've never seen either of you one- millionth as happy...
任何一人有如此快乐
...as you've been since you got together.
你们真的要为了一个房间  放弃这一切吗
Do you really want to throw that all away over a room?
多傻啊
That is so silly.
什么比较重要  爱情
What's more important, love...
还是犯傻
...or silliness?
我们喜欢犯傻
Well, we are fond of the silliness.
但面对爱情也会心软
But we also have a soft spot for the love.
-爱是万灵药  -"欢笑"才是吧
- Love is the best medicine. - That's "laughter."
-你为什么这样  -我不知道
- Why do you do it? - l don't know.
钱德勒
Now, Chandler,
你想跟莫妮卡住吧
you want to live with Monica, right?
对
Yeah, l do.
莫妮卡  你想跟钱德勒住吧
And, Mon, you want to live with Chandler, don't you?
-对  -好
- Yes. - Good.
口头契约在纽约州具有约束力
A verbal contract is binding in the state of New York!
我听说你在找房子
So l understand you're looking for a place?
不  不  我不搬了
No, no, l'm staying put.
我本来打算找你来我家住
l was going to offer you my apartment.
为什么   你要去哪里
Why? Where you going?
我不知道
l don't know.
瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
说了你一定不信
You are not goanna believe it.
钱德勒和莫妮卡又要同居了
Monica and Chandler are moving in again.
真是太好了...对他们来说  对吧
That's great news, right? l mean, for them, right?
不过好处是  我们又能当室友了
But on the bright side, we get to be roommates again.
是啊  关于这件事...
Yeah. You know, about that....
罗斯  我真的感谢
Ross, l really appreciate your offer
你主动提出帮我  但...
to let me move in and everything...but,
-你不觉得这会很怪吗  -为什么
- don't you think it's goanna be weird? - Why?
为什么   为...为什么会怪
Why? Why would it.... Why would it be weird?
你懂的  因为我们
Well, you know, because of us.
因为我们的过去
Because of our history.
-不会  -不会吗
- No! - No?
不会  不会
No, no!
除非我们还余情未了  那就怪了
lt would only be weird if we were still in "that place."
你对我还余情未了吗
Are you still in that place?
-一点也没有  -很好  我也没有
- No, not at all. - Good. Me neither.
那就没问题了
So it's not a problem.
我们只是碰巧是室友的朋友
We're just two friends who happen to be roommates.
但罗斯  我们迟早会各自约会的
Okay, but Ross, eventually you and l will be dating.
真的吗  我们会吗
Really? We are?
是啊  我会交男朋友
Yeah. l'll have a boyfriend
而你会交女朋友
and you'll have a girlfriend.
那太好了
That'd be great.
不过如果你觉得无所谓
But you know what? If you think it'll be okay,
我们可以想出一套方法
we'll just work out a system.
就像大学时代
You know, lt'll be like in college.
我会在门上挂个牌子
I'll hang a hanger on the door and put a sign,
"内有床客  请勿打扰"
"Come back later. l'm getting lucky."
也是  我没想过这个问题
Yeah, l didn't think of that.
你们确定要住在一起吗
So are you sure about this whole moving-in thing?
我是说  这可是大事
l mean it's a really big step.
不能着急
And what's the rush?
真好笑
That's very funny.
他在装傻
He's being silly
因为他知道我们喜欢犯傻
because he knows we enjoy the silliness.
不  我是说真的
No, l'm serious, okay?
你们想想  你一搬进来
I mean, Think about it. You move in.
就为了游戏房的蠢事吵架
You start fighting over a stupid game rooms.
没多久之后  估计就分手啦
Next thing you know, you break up.
罗斯  你之前说得对
Ross, you were right before.
为一间房子吵架很蠢
lt was just a stupid fight about a room.
一点也不蠢
There are no stupid fights!
重点不是房间
This isn't about the room.
而是房间代表什么
This is about what the room represents.
不幸的是  这个房间会毁了你们
And unfortunately, this room could destroy you!
-我没那么担心  -我也是
- l'm not so worried. - Yeah, Me neither.
好吧  反正是你们的人生
Fine. lt's your life!
我只是不想看到你们分手
l just don't want to see you break up, you know.
你们要是同居
Which you will do
就会分手
if you move in together.
但你们想这样  我也没办法
But if that's what you want, there's nothing l can do.
不要同居
Don't do it!
-你还是想搬进来的  对吧  -当然
- You still want to move in together, right? - Of course.
罗斯没吓到你吗
Ross didn't scare you?
吓得我死也不敢跟他住
Scared me out of wanting to live with him.
-我给你看个东西  -好
- l gotta show you something. - Okay.
我的天  正方形人被杀了
Oh, my God! Someone's killed Square Man!
我觉得安乐椅可以放这里
This is where the Barcalounger will go.
你可以看电视
You see, you can see the TV,
离厨房的距离又够近
and it's still walking distance to the kitchen.
真周到
Oh, that's so sweet.
-我也有东西要给你看  -好的
- l want to show you something too. - Okay.
你知道道路会合的标志吧
You know those big road signs that say "merge"?
你知道啊  我在想
You know? So l was thinking that
我们可以弄一个挂在床头
we could get one of those signs and hang it over our bed.
因为你和我就是那样
Because that's you and l together.
合而为一
"Merge!"
-我的天  我超喜欢  -真的吗
-Oh my god! l love that! - Really?
不
"No!"
* 我发现你在我床上 *
* l found you in my bed *
* 你怎么会在那里 *
* How'd you wind up there? *
*你真是个谜 *
* You are a mystery *
* 小黑卷毛男 *
* Little black curly hair *
* 小黑  小黑  小黑 *
* Little black, little black, little black *
* 小黑卷毛男 *
* Little black curly hair *
如果想收到我的演出的电邮
lf you want to receive e-mails about my upcoming shows...
请捐钱给我  好让我买台电脑
please give me money so l can buy a computer.
其他人呢
Where are the other guys?
莫妮卡和钱德在忙
Well, Monica and Chandler are occupied.
-吵架  -不  是忙"别的"
- Fighting? - The other thing.
真高兴他们能和好
l think it's great they worked things out.
谁也别想拆散他们  对吧
There's no breaking them up, is there?
我可以借你的钥匙
Can l borrow the key to your house
-去对面街配把钥匙吗  -当然可以
- so l can run across street to make a copy? - Sure.
-拿去  -谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
你确定吗
Now, are you sure?
配了钥匙就不能反悔了哦
Because once l make a copy, there's no turning back.
我确定
Yeah, l'm sure.
趁我改变心意前快去吧
Now get out of here before l change my mind.
听着  罗斯
Listen, Ross.
你真觉得瑞秋一起住好吗
You really think moving in with Rachel is a good idea?
我也在摇摆不定
l've been back and forth.
也许你应该摆回去
Well, maybe you should go back, okay?
瑞秋一搬进去  不知不觉间
Rachel moves in, and before you know it...
就会发生你们都不想发生的事
...you're right where you don't want to be,
"回头"
back together.
应该不会
l don't think so.
她已经在谈交男朋友的事
She's already talking about, you know, dating other guys.
不会有好结果的
That's not going to work out.
她酒会哭着回家
She'll come home all weepy...
而你则会安慰她说
...and you'll be telling her,
"没关系  你会找到好男人"
"Oh, that's okay. You'll find someone."
紧接着   她找上了你
And then, bam! She finds you!
-也许你说得对  -我告诉你  罗斯
- Maybe you're right. - I am telling you, Ross,
她绝对会再爱上你
she is definitely gonna fall in love with you again.
这样你也愿意吗
ls that what you want?
我愿意吗
ls that what l want?
是的
Yes.
她来了  等着
Here she comes. Hold on.
我来替你省点事
l'm gonna make your life much easier.
五金行打烊了  改天再配
Well, the place was closed, so l'll copy it later.
或是别配了
Or not.
瑞秋  你为何不搬来和我一起住
Rach, why don't you move in with me?
乔伊
Whoa, Joey!
别别别  先别紧张
No, no, no, no, no. It's okay.
瑞秋  我知道赤裸星期四
I mean I...look, Rach, l know l scared you off with
把你吓跑了  但...
that whole naked- Thursdays thing, but...
我们也可以不这样
...we don't have to do that.
搬到对面确实比较轻松
Well, it would be easier to move across the hall.
慢着  除非你想改成赤裸星期三
Wait a minuite, Unless you're thinking about naked Wednesdays.
你不喜欢星期四
Thursday's clearly not good for you.
那就随便挑一天好了
Pick a day!
请进  谢谢你再跑一趟
Come on in. Thanks for coming back.
要知道有很多人对这房间感兴趣
Okay, there's a lot of people interested in the room.
但我经过筛选
But l've narrowed it down,
你是最后人选之一
and you're one of the finalists.
-太好了  -好的  那在做决定之前
- Great! - Okay, now before l make my decision,
我想确定我们是否合得来
l just want to be sure our personalities match, okay?
所以我发明了一个小测验
So l made up a little test.
现在我说一个词
Now l'm gonna say a word,
你就说出你一个想到的事情
and you say the first thing that comes to mind.
-没问题  -好  那我们开始
- l can do that. - Okay, here we go.
-枕头  -仗
- Pillow. - Fight.
很好
Very good.
下一个  丁字
Okay, "G."
-裤  -非常好
- String? - Excellent!
狗
Doggy.
-猫  -很抱歉
- Kitten? - Sorry!
就差那么一点点  再见
So close, though. Bye- bye!